

Name Timotei C. Jugariu

Date of birth 16.10.1996

□ Nationality **Dutch & Romanian**

Email address

Phone number +316 • • • • • •

in LinkedIn in/••••••

Address Netherlands

A Driving Licence AM, B1, B

Curriculum Vitae

Timo Jugariu

About Me An all-round computer scientist with a versatile skill-set and a broad knowledge, I am continuously trying to learn from all the experiences I go through. On top of being technically inclined, I do enjoy perfecting my soft-skills whether it is communicating effectively, taking initiative within a group or everything in between.

Education

Sept 2020 - present

MSc Embedded Systems at Delft University of Technology

- Specialisation: networking and software engineering
- o Other topics covered: big data processing, computer architectures, machine learning.
- o Master thesis (work in progress): syntax-guided program synthesis applied in the context of programmable networks.
- o GPA 8/10

Sept 2019 - July 2020 Minor in Spaceflight at Delft University of Technology, Netherlands

o Topics covered: basics of control theory, signal analysis, spacecraft technology and design and intro to astronomy and remote sensing.

Sept 2016 - July 2020

BSc Computer Science and Engineering at Delft University of Technology, Netherlands

- o Bachelor end project: Computer Vision for Exam grading.
- o Broad curriculum covering software engineering, mathematics, artificial intelligence, computer networks and so on.
- o Electives on operating systems and embedded software; course on Big Data Processing taken for additional credit.
- o GPA 7.9/10

Sept 2011 - July 2015 Grigore Moisil National College of Computer Science, Brasov, Romania

- o "Diplomă de Bacalaureat" earned with a grade of 10/10 for Math and 9.2/10 for Computer Science.
- o The following year I have worked while studying the Dutch language to earn the "Staatsexamen NT2" diploma and attain all other bachelor entry requirements.

Experience

Jan 2020 - May 2020

Front-end Developer at Stantec, Delft, Netherlands

- o Role: implement a new feature to Stantec's Soil Risk Map application and improve other parts of the existing codebase.
- o Technologies: JavaScript (Dojo toolkit, JQuery), Sass, HTML

Feb 2018 - Feb 2020

Teaching Assistant at Delft University of Technology, **Netherlands**

- o Courses: Web and Database Technology, Algorithms and Data Structures.
- o Responsibilities: assisting students during tutorials, grading assignments and exams.
- o Technologies: Java, Node.js, JS, SQL, MongoDB



Github github.com/•••••

Website

Personal qualities

• • • • • • • • • • •

- o result-driven
- o eye for detail
- honest but friendly

Hobbies

- o Tennis
- o Gym

Sept 2018 - Aug 2019 Software Developer at Formula Student Team Delft, Delft, Netherlands

- o Part-time software engineer for one of the most ambitious teams in the Formula Student competition.
- Responsibility: maintaining and testing the C/C++ code that ran on the car's main Electronic Control Unit
- We won Formula Student Netherlands in July 2019.
- Technologies: C/C++, FreeRTOS

July 2018 - Sept 2018 Software Developer Intern at Stabiplan, Brasov, Ro-

- mania • Role: full-stack development while being guided by mentors
- o Technologies: .NET (C#, ASP.NET), SQL, JavaScript

Boon Sliedrecht B.V., Ridderkerk, Netherlands Oct 2015 - Apr 2017

o Part-time order-picker for the Boon distribution center.

Software Development Skills ———

Programming languages

| o Java | **** | o C/C++ | **** |
|--------------------------------|-------|---------------------------|---------------|
| JavaScript | *** | Node.js | *** |
| Python | *** | o SQL | *** |
| o HTML & CSS | *** | o C# | *** |
| o Scala | **** | o PHP | ★★★☆☆ |
| o x86-64 Assembly | *** | o ASP.NET | *** |
| o React | ★★☆☆☆ | o VHDL | ★ ☆☆☆☆ |

Tools & frameworks

| o Git | **** | Apache Spark | *** |
|----------------------------------|-------|-----------------------------------|-------|
| o Apache Kafka | *** | Kafka Streams | **** |
| Docker | ★★★☆☆ | Android SDK | ★★★☆☆ |
| Apache Flink | ★★☆☆☆ | o LaTeX | **** |
| MongoDB | ★☆☆☆☆ | | |

Computer Software

| Microsoft Office | **** | o Linux | ★★★☆☆ |
|--------------------------------------|----------------|---------|-------|
| o Adobe Premier | ★★↑ 5^5 | | |

Communication Skills -

Languages

English (CEFR level: C2), Dutch (CEFR level: C1), Romanian (native).

Volunteering -

Sept 2021 - Sept 2022 Sponsoring committee D.S.T.V. Obvius, Delft, Netherlands

o Responsibilities: acquire new sponsors and keep the existing partnerships going to provide the association with the necessary income.